

Grayson

Taylor

Contact

Address:

Alexandar 50, Toronto, Canada

Email:

champion5star247963@gmail.com

Skype:

live:.cid.e07bcb612fe88d1b

Skills

- React JS
- React Native
- Vue.js
- Express.js
- Django
- Laravel
- Node.js
- Javascript
- Typescript
- Python
- PHP
- MongoDB
- PostgreSQL
- MySQL

Language

• English C1

Summary

I am a passionate senior full-stack web and cross-platform mobile engineer with 8+ years of experience delivering software from MVPs to million-user web apps. My experience span a variety of industries, including education, travel, health, and social media. I pride myself on dependable communication and high-quality deliveries.

Skill Highlights

- User friendly UX/UI
- API building and Integration
- Soket IO
- Database design
- Good communication

Experience

Senior Full Stack Software Developer - 04/2019 to 03/2022 ITM HOUSE, Toronto, Canada

- Created a dashboard-style platform for restauranteurs to monitor the performance of their online delivery orders across marketplaces.
- Prototyped a cross-platform mobile application for the aviation industry to digitize cockpit activities for smallplane pilots.
- Developed order-processing software for a uniforms distributor that reduced order processing time by 90% and handled over \$10,000 in sales volume per month.

Full Stack Web Developer - 07/2015 to 07/2018 NOVISMART TECH., Wien, Austria

- Overhauled a failure-prone, outdated, and missioncritical revenue calculator to reduce annual errors by over 90%, resulting in savings of \$500,000.
- Developed a user-friendly single-page web app for which we hired a team of 12 quality assurance agents.
- Optimized an internal booking search tool to reduce average response time from seven seconds to 300 milliseconds with a significant MySQL load decrease.

Education

Bachelor of Degree in **Computer Science** - 2013 **Helsinki University**, Helsinki, Finland 2008 - 2013

Certification

Certified Web and Mobile Application Developer